Guide to the School of Architecture, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 2005-2010; Accession 2018-A-001
  - Course Evaluations
    - Moon, Kyoung Sun: Arch 2211-Structures and Facades of Tall Buildings, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Darling, Michele Naomi: Arch 2213-Sustainable Design, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Addington, Michelle: Arch 2220-Studies and Light and Materials, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Martin, Allan: Arch 2226-Design Computation, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Sample, Hilary: Arch 2227-Design and Disease, New Typologies, 2009 Fall (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Caldiera, Marta: Arch 3021-Case Studies in Architectural Theory, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Koetter, Alfred: Arch 3071-Issues in Architecture and Urban Design, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Britton, Karla: Arch 3091-Methods and Research, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Ota, Hideaki: Arch 3212-Modern Japanese Architecture, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Wiseman, Carter: Arch 3217-Writing on Architecture, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Harrison, Ariane: Arch 3218-Architectural Theories and Environment, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Sherer, Daniel: Archi 3222-Venice, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Stern, Robert A.M.: Arch 3223-Parallels of the Modern, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Sakamoto, Dean: Arch 3227: Tropical Adventure, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Garvin, Alexander: Arch 4021-Introduction to Architectural Planning, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Hayden, Dolores: Arch 4212-American Cultural Landscapes, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Fuermann, Bryan: Arch 4222-History of Italian Landscape, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - John-Alder, Kathleen: Arch 4225-Learning from Landscape, 2009 Fall (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Visualization I, 2010 Summer (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Visualization IV, 2010 Summer (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Unofficial transcripts-Class of 2005 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Course list, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Course evaluations
    - Gage, Mark Foster: Arch 501-Architectural Design, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Krumwiede, Keith: Arch 503-Architectural Design, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Koetter, Alfred: Arch 509-Post Professional Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Mitchell, Edward: Arch 509-Post Professional Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Knight, George: Arch 511-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Krier, Leon: Arch 511-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Scolari, Masimo: Arch 513-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Newton, Timothy: Arch 513-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Tsien, Billie: Arch 515-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Benner, Andrew: Arch 515-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Eisenman, Peter: Arch 517-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Lourie, Ariane: Arch 517-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Prince-Ramus, Joshua: Arch 519-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Tang, H. Frederick: Arch 519-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Ella, Erez: Arch 519-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Griffith, Sean: Arch 521-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Holland, Charles: Arch 521-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Jacob, Sam: Arch 521-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Johnson, Nick: Arch 521-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Harwell, Andrei S.: Arch 521-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Plattus, Alan J.: Arch 523-Advanced Design Studio, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Axley, James: Arch 601-Structures I, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Chadwick, Aran: Arch 625-Liquid Threshold, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Thomas, Neil: Arch 625-Liquid Threshold, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Addington, Michelle: Arch 633-Environmental Design, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Bellew, Patrick: Arch 633-Environmental Design, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Axley, James: Arch 636-Sustainable Design, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Bernstein, Phillip: Arch 655-Architectural Practice, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Rothroe, Kevin: Arch 665-Materials Formation in Design, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Jacobson, John: Arch 674-Architectural Product Design and Innovation, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Suter, Lindsey: Arch 674-Architectural Product Design and Innovation, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Pell, Benjamin: Arch 690-Display and Fabrication, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Forster, Kurt: Arch 701-Modern Architecture, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Eversole, Gary Britt: Arch 701-Modern Architecture, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Osman, Michael: Arch 704-Case Studies in Architectural Theory, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Petit, Emannuel J.: Arch 704-Case Studies in Architectural Theory, 2007 Fall (Box 2, Folder 55)